We're going to tell you how to make biodiesel from all the different types of oils that are out there.
Biodiesel can be made from all sorts of different things.
We've just settled our oil.
I'm going to take my goggles off here and get back down to talking about how we make biodiesel.
First of all, this is canola oil.
I just picked it up at a local grocery store.
This is vegetable oil.
It's actually soy bean oil if you look on the back, the most common thing in the United States.
This is corn oil and believe it or not, this is oil that came from french fries that were fried.
All of these things, I can make biodiesel out of.
It's very easy to do.
All I have to have is an organic oil to do it.
I'm going to show you how to do it a little bit later here.
But I wanted to show you that you can actually make biodiesel from all sorts of different oils.
Any kind of organic oil.
This is macadamia nut oil.
This is soy bean oil biodiesel.
So, these are biodiesels that we've made.
This is olive oil based biodiesel.
This is another macadamia nut.
This is waste vegetable oil.
This one is corn oil.
And this one is hemp seed oil.